{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Carpet Cleaning Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40005/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40005,"taskName":"Carpets or Rugs - Clean at Home","taskDescription":"Clean Carpets or Rugs in a Home","xmTaskDescriptor":"Carpet Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":33,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Carpet cleaners rug dryclean cleaning","textMessagingName":"Clean Rug in Home","rolloverLongDesc":"Used for wall-to-wall carpets as well as area rugs. Includes such techniques as dry-foam extraction, \"steam cleaning\" \u0026 wiping techniques. This category is not for the rental of do-it-yourself cleaning machines.","rolloverShortDesc":"Carpets cleaned in the home or office.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Carpets or Rugs in a Home.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Area Rug Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Oriental, Persian \u0026 Wool Rug Cleaning Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":10,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Home Carpets or Rugs","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Carpets or Rugs - Clean at Home","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Carpet Cleaning Project","urlName":"Carpets-or-Rugs-Clean-at-Home","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Area Rug Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Oriental, Persian, Wool Rug Cleaners","searchKeywords":"Carpet,cleaners,rug,dryclean,cleaning,service,dry-foam,steam,cleaning","emcCategoryOid":-12011,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your carpet cleaning project","primaryQuestionSetId":329,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40005/":{"taskOID":40005,"originalTaskOID":40005,"setID":329,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4024,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Carpet Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms need carpet cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6019,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stair Landing","answerDisplayText":"Stair Landing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5239,"questionDisplayText":"Method of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning process do you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6062,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Steam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":590,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","answerDisplayText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2097,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17324,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5615,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4026,"questionDisplayText":"Level of Preparation for Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of preparation is necessary?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201802,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4024,"questionDisplayText":"Rooms for Carpet Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which rooms need carpet cleaning?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6019,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stair Landing","answerDisplayText":"Stair Landing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2908,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Hall(s)","answerDisplayText":"Hall(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6019,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stair Landing","answerDisplayText":"Stair Landing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2241,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Entry","answerDisplayText":"Entry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6022,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Stairs","answerDisplayText":"Stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5239,"questionDisplayText":"Method of Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning process do you prefer?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6062,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Steam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":590,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","answerDisplayText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2097,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17324,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5615,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6062,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Steam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":590,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","answerDisplayText":"Carbonated Cleaning Process","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2097,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Dry Foam Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17324,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","answerDisplayText":"Low Moisture Cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5615,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","answerDisplayText":"Shampoo Cleaning Method","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4026,"questionDisplayText":"Level of Preparation for Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of preparation is necessary?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201802,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4400,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Only clean exposed carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3984,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","answerDisplayText":"Move furniture and clean entire carpet area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":201802,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner will move furniture out in advance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}